Amanda Sacco

Web Designer and Developer

Contact

Profile

1317 Pharaoh Rd, 84123 West Valley, Ut 801 864-5331 amandass1@hotmail.com I have a bachelor's from UNISO in Nutrition and a certificate from IGA in Gastronomy and I'm currently studying Web Design and Web Development at SLCC. I have around 1 year of experience in clinical nutrition, public health nutrition, and community nutrition. I am pro-active, meticulous and great at teamwork. I believe in continual professional development through research and teamwork. I take great pleasure in learning new things, practicing outdoor sports and meeting new people.

Education

Experience

Salt Lake Community College April – September 2019 Web Design and Development HTML, CSS, JS, PHP/MySQL April 2017 – May 2017 Nutritionist • Nutrition Intern • Sodexo

Responsible for nutrition paperwork, food safety and kitchen staff training.

University of Sorocaba 2017 Bachelors – Food and Nutrition May 2017 – Jun 2017

Nutritionist • Nutrition Intern • Nutrifam

Responsible for checking on food preparation and storage ensuring food safety, kitchen organization and variety of different healthy meals daily; and responsible for food education classes with the kids.

Skills

Aug 2017 - Sep 2017

Nutritionist • Nutrition Intern • Uniso Health Center

Responsible for providing scheduled patients personalized diets and professional health advices in order to prevent or treat specific health conditions/ symptoms.

Creative thinking
Active Listening
Multilingual
Motivated worker
Great team player

Sep 2017 - Nov 2017

Nutritionist • Nutrition Intern • Evangelical Hospital

Responsible for reading and interpreting medical records and communicating with all patients.

Technical Skills

Interpersonal communication

Languages

Microsoft Word
Power Point
Excel

English: Full professional proficiency Spanish: Elementary proficiency

Photoshop

Portuguese: Native

HTML, CSS, JS, PHP/MySQL